立定
Guard, halt.
手铐
Handcuffs.
向左转
Left turn.
下士
Corporal.
快,出来！出来列队！
Come on, let's have you! Get fell in!
出来点名！出来！
It's roll call! Let's have you!
- 军士,看看其它房间  - 跑步！
- Sergeant, check the other huts.   - Quick march, double!
快！跟上！跟上！
Come on! Move! Move!
听到没？！出来点名,否则早餐要喝血了！
Come on! Fall out for roll call, or it's blood for breakfast!
施莱特上尉有话给佩里上校
Kapitan Schleutter's compliments to Major Perry.
他只和上校谈
He will speak only to the Major.
话筒给我
The P.A.
施莱特上尉,你的人必须出来集合点名
Captain Schleutter, your men will now fall in for roll call...
其中25人要带手铐,这是必须的
and 25 of them will be handcuffed, as previously ordered.
你的国家违反日内瓦协议,挑起这一切
Your country started this in violating the Geneva Convention.
在德国的路德维希斯多夫监狱,25名英国军官
Twenty-five British officers were shackled...
被带了手铐
in Ludwigsdorf Prison in Germany.
点名后,必须铐起来25名军官
After roll call, we must handcuff 25 of your officers...
施莱特上尉
Captain Schleutter.
你准备怎么做呢,上校？
How do you plan to do that, Major?
我们有600个人,我们不同意
There are 600 of us and we don't agree.
你是在逼我用暴力
You leave me no alternative but to result to force.
好斗的家伙,是吧？
Bloody man. I mean, can't he see?
主演：布莱恩・凯斯
片名：暴动战俘营
主演：赫尔穆特・格里姆
伊安・亨德利
毫无意义
There's nothing for it.
- 带他们过来  - 是,长官
- Bring 'em up.   - Yes, sir.
考科斯上校,把那些人带到这里
Major Cox, bring those men up here.
原地踏步！
Squad, mark time!
立定！
Squad, halt!
长官！
Sir!
考科斯先生,进入一号房
Mr. Cox, enter barracks number one...
逮捕施莱特上尉
and place Captain Schleutter under arrest.
是,长官！开门！
Y es, sir! Gates!
跑步,走！
Company, double march!
来呀,我们走！
Come on, let's go!
我不参与,明白吗？
I want no part of this, understand?
卫兵听着...
All guard towers...
这是佩里上校
this is Major Perry.
不要开枪...
There is to be no shooting...
除非犯人越过警戒线
unless a prisoner crosses the trip wire.
明白吗？
Is that understood?
停火
Cease firing.
出来,你这德国脏猪！
Come out, you kraut swine!
你干吗不进来？！
Why don't you come in here?!
狗娘养的！
Bastards!
催泪弹准备
Gas grenades in.
催泪弹,他们过线了
Tear gas, they're past the wire.
快！快点！
Come on! Double it up!
我要12个人。6人跟着我,6人去后面
I want 12 men. Six with me and six around the back.
快速行动！去另一边！
Those men, pronto! Cover the other side!
退后站成一线！
Drop back and form a line!
上刺刀！
Fix bayonets!
塔楼士兵听着...
All guard towers...
他们越过警戒线就开枪
there is to be no shooting unless they cross the trip wire.
士兵,站好岗位！
Soldiers, stand guard!
冲上去！
Move it up!
快！去那里！围住那边
Hurry up! Get in there! Go round that side.
是德国空军...关键时候
Is the Luftwaffe...above all this.
快  - 走啊
Come on   - get going.
去死吧
Go to the devil.
真是一群傻蛋
What a bunch of idiots.
把英国兵弄出去。出去！...出去！...出去！
Get the Tommies out of here. Out!...Out!...Out!
关上门！
Close the gates!
把你的手拷送回伦敦吧,佩里上校
Send your handcuffs back to London, Major Perry.
施莱特上尉,日内瓦协议授权与我
Captain Schleutter, I'm entitled by the Geneva Convention...
惩罚你们这怪诞的行为！
to punish you and your men for this incredible behavior!
你们将被限食限行动48小时
You'll be confined to your huts on restricted diet for 48 hours!
所有的优待及电力
All privileges and electric power...
将被缩减
will be curtailed for that period.
限制结束后
And at the end of that period...
你们要有秩序地集合点名
you will fall in for roll call in proper order.
就象现在这样
As indeed you are now.
把你的手拷送回伦敦,否则离开我们的营地
Send your handcuffs back to London and stay out of our camp until you do.
你和某个军人发生关系
Did you have relations with an enlisted personnel...
康纳上尉？
Captain Connor?
是的,长官
I did, sir.
她是自愿的
She was willing.
你是否打了海军军官？
Did you strike an officer of His Majesty's Navy?
没有,我只说了些事
Not at all. I said something or other.
他推了我一下,没什么
He gave me a sort of push. It wasn't anything.
警察报告中写着“恶化事态的攻击”
The police report called it "aggravated assault."
是吗？
Did it?
记录显示你是
Your past record indicates that you were...
和4个军人喝醉了...
drunk with four enlisted men...
擅离职守
and absent without leave...
6次
six times.
现在你等候调职
Even though you are currently awaiting orders for your next posting...
并不是说可以忽视条例...
that is not a license to ignore military regulations...
给军队带来耻辱
and bring disgrace to the uniform.
是,长官
Yes, sir.
根据记录
It is within the authority of this review board...
要降低你的职位使用
to reduce you in rank to the lowest commissioned rating.
然而,我们应情报部要求
However, we have been requested to hold our decision in abeyance...
暂停处理
by His Majesty's lntelligence.
- 克尔将军有话问你  - 是本・克尔？
- General Kerr wishes to question you.   - Ben Kerr?
又乱套了不是,杰克？
So it's a balls-up again, eh, Jack?
将军总是觉得军队糟糕才象个将军
The army must be in a bad way for generals, makin' you one.
- 你总算明白了些  - 一个编辑在军队能干什么？
- You've got that bit right at least.   - What's an editor do in the army?
写希特勒的性生活然后发给报纸？
Write stories about Hitler's sex life and send 'em off to the newspapers?
我们让象你这样的怪才歪才工作,来赢得战争
We put corrupt and ill-assorted talents like yours to work winning the war.
我已要求调你来情报部
I've requested your transfer to lntelligence.
你怎么会这样做？
Why in hell you want to do that?
你去管理苏格兰的战俘营
You're going to run a P.O.W. camp in Scotland.
饶了我吧,本。我不是警察
God, Benny. I'm not a policeman.
去你的好记者吧！
Damn good crime reporter, though.
自从我认识你,你就是个不安分的家伙
You've been a chaotic bastard for as long as I've known you.
但你总是有不正当的天赋,把周围的事情理顺
But you have a perverse sort of genius for setting things in order around you--
只要你有心去做
when you've a mind to.
我现在有心去度假
I've a mind to go on a holiday at the moment.
记录里说你度过假了
Well, that review board will see that you get it.
杰克,我是在救你这高贵的爱尔兰蠢蛋
Jack, I'm saving your royal lrish ass for you...
让你有机会做适合你的工作
and giving you the chance to do the sort of job you've always been keen on doing.
战俘？我吐,长官
Prisoners of war? I puke, sir.
别废话了,杰克.
Now get stuffed, Jack.
我需要你,我非常需要你那非凡的感应力
I need you. I need your great nose to the ground.
麦肯齐的德军战俘,全是高级官员
The German prisoners, all top-line officers...
在过去几个月里,一直在制造麻烦
have been raising a peculiar sort of hell at McKenzie the past few months.
其它地方相对平静
Other camps, relative quiet.
麦肯齐,实际上是失控
McKenzie, veritable state of siege.
作战部和情报部都想知道他们
Both War Office and lntelligence want to find out if there's any connection...
是否与德国有联系
any link with the dear old Deutschland.
你被授全权
You have full authorization...
做任何必做之事,恢复营地的秩序
to do what you must to bring the camp around...
找出我们想知道的
and find out what we need to know.
佩里上校现负责那里
A Major Perry's in command there.
让上尉指挥上校管理营地？
The captain tells the major how to run his camp?
那让你好笑吧
I thought that would amuse you.
他将收到指令和情报部合作
He'll be instructed to cooperate with Military lntelligence and so on.
那记录怎么处理？
What about that review board?
你有办法不让那来骚扰我吗？
Have you any ideas how to keep them off my back?
我会处理的,老家伙
I shall ponder the matter, old boy.
能来点治痢疾
Can you give me something for diarrhea...
头痛或便秘的吗？
headache or constipation?
好的,他来了-- 佩里上校！
Yes, here he comes-- Major Perry!
说英语
English. English.
为什么那些孩子打斗？
Why are those boys fighting?
为什么校长不制止他们？
Why does that schoolmaster not stop them?
他来了--佩里上校！
Here he comes-- Major Perry!
安静...安静,还有节目
Quiet...quiet. There's more to come.
谁再吹口哨将罚款10马克
The next one who whistles will be fined 10 marks.
英国人都有个肥屁股
All the English have fat asses
佩里上校,考科斯军士
Major Perry, Sergeant Cox
我们想给他们带手铐
We would like to give them handcuffs
把他们关进6英尺的箱子
Put them in a six-feet box
当战争结束
When the war is gone and finished
我们赢得胜利
And we win the victory
德国将会更大
Deutschland then will be much bigger
英格兰则属于你和我
England then belongs to you and me
当战争结束
When the war is gone and finished
我们赢得胜利
And we win the victory
德国将会更大
Deutschland then will be much bigger
英格兰则属于你和我
England then belongs to you and me
我们可留在麦肯齐战俘营
We can stay in Camp McKenzie
因为英格兰属于你和我
For England then belongs to you and me
为司令官施吕特欢呼
Three cheers for Commandant Schluetter...
...万岁
...hip hip, hooray.
这是个血腥的英国杂耍戏院
It's a bloody English music hall.
没有英国兵能有意思吗？
Is more fun in here without the English Tommies, eh?
你们  - 谢谢今早演出
All of you   - thanks for this morning.
你扮了个恶心的英国女人,施密特
You make a lousy English lady, Schmidt.
她太象犹太人了！
She's too Jewish looking!
诺伊尔,你应该参加
Neuchl, you should take the part.
你扮来一定很象英国女人
You'd make a hell of an English lady.
为何不带你的朋友伯杰到台上来
Why not bring your friend, Berger, up here to the stage...
给我们模仿两个英国女人的做派？
and do the sketch for us like two English ladies?
行吗？
Won't you?
你的地位并不是用来这样侮辱我的
Your position, Kapitan, is not so to give me such insult.
作为你的长官,我的地位是...
My position as your commanding officer is so...
因懦弱枪毙你
to have you killed for being a coward, if I must.
你不是懦夫吗？
Are you not a coward?
我遵守战犯规则
I obey the rules of a prisoner of war.
做为德国战俘营司令官...
As the German Camp Commandant...
...你知道日内瓦协议不允许煽动骚乱
...you know the Geneva Convention forbids you to incite a riot.
你是个同性恋,不是吗？
You are a homosexual, are you not?
对不起,你英语很差
Sorry. Your English is poor.
你是个同性恋,是不是？
You're a queer aren't you?
为何不让伯杰上台来？
Why don't you ask Berger here to the stage?
你们可拥抱接吻,来一个可爱的同性恋婚礼
You can hug and kiss and have a lovely queer wedding.
我会再找你的
I'll see you later.
去他的规定吧,让我们点起胜利之火
To hell with orders, let's make a victory fire.
是的,考科斯先生,烟火之夜
Quite right, Mr. Cox. Fireworks night.
他们在蔑视灯火管制
They're flaunting the blackout regulations, sir.
是的,庆祝48小时的处罚
Yes, celebrating my 48-hour punishment.
- 我们等着看吧  - 等着看什么？
- We'll see to that, sir.   - You'll see to what?
等着看我们又被耍了一次
You'll see to it that we're all made fools of once again.
你不能派人去执行灯火管制吗？
Will you move men in there to enforce blackout regulations?
等到那里,他们会都跑了,又笑话我们
Jerry will have disappeared by the time you get there, laughing at us.
你的人会少几个头被打破的
Your men will get a few more broken heads for their pains.
这帮好斗的德国佬点火指引空袭
The bleeding krauts are lightin' up the sky askin' for a raid, sir.
在这荒凉的鸡场100英里范围内,从没有过空袭！
There's never been a raid within 100 miles of this desolate chicken farm!
只有警报。我是说,怎么会炸这里呢？
Only alerts. I mean, why bomb this?
这里人员不足、设备简陋,很平常的边区村落
This understaffed, ill-manned outpost of military mediocrities.
谢谢,没事的
Thank you. That'll be all.
安排一下从伦敦来的康纳上尉
Make transport arrangements for a Captain Connor coming up from London.
- 详细资料在连部  - 是,长官
- The details are in the orderly room.   - Yes, sir.
把棋下完怎样,霍尔先生？
Shall we finish the game, Mr. Hall?
随你
As you like, sir.
对不起
Sorry.
我有点过份
I went a bit too far.
真不知道英国政府怎么想的
I'm damned if I know what Whitehall expects.
"别太过份了,我们有很多人在德国战俘营里"
"Don't move too aggressively. Thousands of our chaps in German prison camps."
这我赞成
And I quite agree.
"但你就不能维持那里的秩序吗,佩里上校？"
"But can't you maintain order there, Major Perry?"
我要求增加兵力,他们却只派来个康纳上尉
And when I ask for troop reinforcements, they send me a single Captain Connor.
"让他处理一下这个事情",我是说,唉
"Let him have a look at the matter." I mean, oh, dear.
穿上这军服,你比警卫还象英国人
With those uniforms you look more British than the Guard.
没人会阻拦你出大门
No one will stop you once you are out of the gate.
是我们的苏格兰联络人
It's our Scottish contact.
他在格伦福伊尔大街,等霍奇鲍尔和施密特
He'll be waiting for Hochbauer and Schmidt on the Glenfoyle Road.
好
Good.
B 代表柏林和暴动
B is for Berlin and breakout.
柏林方面怎么说？
What did Berlin say?
说英语,这不是柏林
English. It wasn't Berlin.
是我们这里的苏格兰朋友
It was our friend here in Scotland...
他同意提前见你
and he agrees to an earlier meeting with you.
佩里要我们带手铐时,我们大闹一场
Let's raise a little hell when Perry tries to put on the handcuffs...
你可以直接出去,混进英国人中
and you can march straight off and join the British army.
我刚来时我们常在这里野炊,很棒的
We used to have picnics here when I first came. It was grand.
德国小伙子很孤独,很可爱
They were so lonely, the German lads, and they were so nice.
然后制定了规定,缩紧了营地
Then they made the rule, I guess. Closed the camp tight.
什么时候的事？
When was that?
有一年吧,头来的时候
About a year ago, when the headmaster came.
呃,是上校。佩里上校,是的
Uh, the Major. Major Perry, that is.
佩里上校来的时候
When Major Perry came, sir.
一帮弱不经风的家伙
You're a bunch of weaklings.
该空军的了
Now it's the Lufwaffe's turn.
早晨好,施莱特上尉
Good morning, Captain Schleutter.
谢谢你早晨送来了名单
Thank you for the list you sent me this morning.
但还有其他英语讲得很好的
But there are others of us who speak excellent English.
你英语很好,克兰兹
Your English is excellent, Kranz.
地道在你来前就开始挖了
The tunnel was begun before you came here.
名单上要逃离的人28人,都是潜艇上的人
Your list, the 28 men who are to escape, are all U-boat men.
没我的人,也没有昂格尔的技师
None of my men. None of Unger's engineers.
我掌控地道,是受命于希特勒和邓尼茨
I took the tunnel over on orders from Hitler and Doenitz.
是为了让有技术的潜艇人员返回战争
In order to get skilled U-boat men back into the war.
德国现在需要他们
Germany must have them now.
我明白,但我的人需要些解释
I understand, but my men want some explanation.
你是空军司令官,你解释命令吗？
You're a Luftwaffe Commandant. Do you explain orders?
我要你解释为何那样对待诺伊尔
I want some explanation about the way you treated Neuchl.
那个仙女,他是个德国孬种
That flying fairy, Hauptman, he's a bad German.
是的,我在爱尔兰度过一两个很惬意的假
Yes, I've spent a very decent holiday or two in lreland.
为什么中止了战俘在外活动的待遇？
What made you decide to suspend the outside privileges for the Germans?
我觉得我前任对制度太随意了
I felt that my predecessor had taken too many liberties with regulations.
事实上,冯・威斯托芬和我协议--
As a matter of fact, Von Westhofen agreed with me--
是营中官衔最高的,直到他4月份死去
the German senior officer in the camp until his death last April.
好老头,冯・威斯托芬将军
Nice old boy, General Von Westhofen.
很爱看书
A great feeling for books.
现在是个年轻的魔鬼负责,你听说过施莱特吗？
Complete opposite of the young devil now in command. You've heard of Schleutter?
听说过。那老头怎么死的？
Yes. What did the nice old boy die of?
- 自然死亡？  - 心脏病发作
- A natural death?   - Heart attack.
早安
Morning.
康纳上尉是伦敦派来的
Captain Connor's been sent up from London.
他来协助我分析这里的情况
He's to assist me in analyzing the problems here.
48小时的处罚什么时候结束？
When are you goin' to lift your 48-hour siege, sir?
明早起床号时
Tomorrow morning at reveille.
- 我们进去看看  - 不要,上尉
- Let's have a look inside then.   - I think not, Captain.
会减弱处罚的效果
It would weaken the effect of the punishment.
我要四处看看
I should have a look around.
上尉,昨天在那里有12个人受重伤
Captain, 12 men were seriously injured in there yesterday.
若你进去,是你的责任
If you go in, it's your responsibility.
好的
Yes, sir.
- 那电话通所有岗楼吗？  - 是的长官
- Does that phone go to all the towers?   - Yes, sir.
对不起
Excuse me.
我是康纳上尉
This is Captain Connor speaking.
我要进去了
I'm comin' inside now.
你也来好吗,考科斯先生？
Will you come along, Mr. Cox?
增援  - 一个新人！
Reinforcements   - one more man!
看来我们来客了
Looks like we have company.
你认为冯・威斯托芬是怎么死的,考科斯先生？
What do you suppose Von Westhofen died of, Mr. Cox?
就象佩里上校所说,先生
I expect it was as Major Perry said, sir.
我想知道你的看法
I'd like your opinion on that.
我看他一直很健康
Well, he always seemed in the best of health to me, sir.
你认为施莱特除掉了他？
You think Schleutter got rid of him?
那狗娘养的控制了这里,我就知道这些
The bastard has control now. That's all I know.
- 有人逃走过吗？  - 有几个
- Have you had any escapes?   - A few.
大多数在妓院被抓回来
Most of them get picked up in the local whorehouse.
有两人成功地逃到了爱尔兰自由州
A couple did make it across to the lrish Free State.
你是说地狱吧,去了可怕的地方
Hell, you say. Horrible place to wind up.
只有一个办法对付战犯
There's only one way to handle prisoners, sir.
把他们关进足够小的的地方
Lock 'em up someplace so tight...
使他们只能吃、睡和拉屎
that all they can do is eat, sleep and shit.
但日内瓦协议不容许
But the Geneva Convention wouldn't abide it.
他们有工场吗？
Do they have any workshops?
他们可以制造出你说的任何东西
They can make almost anything you care to name.
把他们军官的军服搞得象新的一样
Made uniforms as good as new for their top officers.
他们有焊锅匠、裁缝
They've got the lot: tinkers, tailors.
- 造烛台的,我不奇怪  - 他们造过枪吗？
-Candlestick makers, I shouldn't wonder. -Did they make any guns yet?
我们搜过,突然搜查,什么也没找到
We search, we try to surprise them. We find nothing.
好象我们总是在诧异
It turns out we always get the surprises.
- 那是施莱特吗？  - 是,一号房
- Is that Schleutter?   - Ay, number one barracks.
肯定
To be sure.
"沉默的威利"
"Quiet Willi."
而他的人并不沉默,是他负责
His men aren't so quiet, though. He's seen to that.
他得到了比在潜艇上更大的权力.
He's got more authority here than he ever had on a U-boat.
我昨天听说了他在军事演习中的表现
I heard about his playin' at war games yesterday.
- 很刺激,是不是？  - 太对了,长官
- Exciting, was it?   - You're dead right, sir.
那里是食堂。拐角处是冷却器
That's the mess hall up there. Around the corner is the cooler.
上校还没充分利用它
The Major hasn't made enough use of it yet, sir.
有这帮人你烦不烦？
Are you irritated by this lot?
- 没他们更好,长官  - 那就走快点
- I could do without them, sir.   - Quick march, then.
表层土很好,威利
That's lovely topsoil, Willi.
对你的萝卜视察满意吗,上尉？
Were you satisfied with your turnip inspection, Captain?
很满意
Just grand.
你把地道的土放在那里,是不是？
You're not puttin' the dirt from your tunnel there, are you?
地道？你过时了,上尉
Tunnel? You're old-fashioned, Captain.
没错
That's right.
是的,肯定有比地道更好的办法
Yes, there must be a better way than that.
请注意
Attention, please.
我是佩里上校
This is Major Perry.
我指派康纳上尉负责明天的点名
I am assigning Captain Connor officer in charge of roll call tomorrow morning.
他将监督挑选和上手铐
He will supervise the selection and handcuffing...
点名后25名军官带手铐
of 25 German officers immediately after roll call.
谢谢
Thank you.
该有更好的办法
There must be a better way.
我们把这入口与2号房隔开
We keep this entrance from N.2. barracks clear...
因为这是主要的逃跑入口
...since it is the main escape hatch.
若你跟我去3号
If you will follow me to No.3.
就能看到顶层
You can inspect the Attic there.
过厕所时小心
Careful climbing through the latrine closet.
到顶层才有光
There is no light until the Attic.
我计算过天花板的负荷
I have calculated the load on the ceiling.
我们有1千7百立方厘米的垃圾
We have 17,000 cubic centimeters of dirt.
我用绳索来固定
I've installed cable supports...
粗糙但有效
...crude but effective.
在预计时间内很难完成
It's difficult with the advanced schedule.
在逃跑的人中没有激励机制
We don't have the incentive of being among those to escape.
当然,解决这个问题要给我足够的奖励
Of course solving the problem is incentive enough for me.
我是工程师
I am an engineer.
做个效率高的工程师,昂格尔
Be a fast engineer, Unger.
我们距篱笆5米
We are five meters from the fence...
距河流26米
...and 26 meters from the stream.
我们要用2号房的房顶空间
We will have to use the roof space in Barracks 2.
3号房就要装满了
Barracks 3 will soon be filled.
- 早晨好,考科斯先生  - 早晨好,长官
- Good evening, Mr. Cox.   - Good evening, sir.
- 你下令6点吹起床号  - 是的
- You ordered reveille at 0600 hours.   - That's right.
C连25人带手铐
And C Company to fall out with 25 handcuffs.
对
Right.
叫消防队,好吗？
And call the fire brigade, will you?
- 消防队  - 长官
- Fire brigade.   - Sir.
把他们从前两个等级分开
Divide them between the front two ranks.
每级别两个
Two to each rank.
半面左转
Half left, wheel.
右转！
Right wheel!
我是康纳上尉
This is Captain Connor speaking.
所有犯人听着：要立即点名
To all prisoners: There'll be immediate roll call.
重复：立即点名,25人要带手铐
I repeat: There'll be an immediate roll call and 25 men will be handcuffed.
按计划进入营地
Enter the barracks as previously instructed.
行动！
Move!
没人,长官。空的
Nobody here, sir. Dead empty. Mother Hubbard.
这里也是,长官
Same here, sir.
小心检查
Proceed with caution.
6人去2号,跑步！
Six men to hut two. On the double!
快进去
Move in quickly.
回来！
Get back!
不要太认真了
You don't have to make it look this realistic.
放松点,你不必杀我的
Take it easy, you don't have to kill me.
你们两个！
Hey, you two men!
回来！
Get back!
好,去那里,混进英国人里
Good, now get in there and mix with the British.
德国佬上钩了
Jerry's taking the bait.
注意,这猪叫了消防队
Watch out, the swines have called the Fire Brigade.
快
Hurry.
考科斯,打开！
Mr. Cox, turn it on!
该空军出来了,带诺伊尔来
It's time for the Luftwaffe. Get Neuchl.
4人跟我来
Four men with me.
抓住那人！
Get that man!
铐上那狗娘养的
Handcuff the bastards.
考科斯,行了
Mr. Cox, that'll do.
关了！
Off!
看来你赢了手铐的争执,上尉
You seem to have won an argument over handcuffs, Captain.
你都湿透了,威利
And you got all wet, Willi.
让你的人1小时后点名
Have your men out in one hour for roll call.
我坚持立刻去医院
I insist on visiting your infirmary immediately...
看看我的人的情况
to see to the condition of my men.
点名后才行,威利
Right after the roll call, Willi.
- 说英语  - 好的
- And speak English.   - Okay.
我也很高兴出来。但我们必须找到在凯思尼斯的朋友
I'm glad to be out too. But we have to find our chum in Cathness.
他在说什么？
What the hell is he sayin'?
我想他是昏迷了,长官
I think he's unconscious, sir.
他醒后我要和他讲话
When he comes around I want to talk to him.
- 不惜代价  - 我尽力
- Do whatever you have to.   - Do my best.
那人状况很差,我们的人没必要那么过份
That man's in a very bad way. Our chaps didn't have to go that far.
不是我们的人打的
It wasn't them that did it to him.
是他们自己人,几乎杀了他
It was his own lot. Damn near killed him.
或许出于私人恩怨
Working off some private grudge, perhaps.
长官,刚收到的
Sir, this just came.
派一个人守着他,不要让任何人接近他
Keep a close guard on him, Sergeant. I don't want anyone near him.
- 康纳上尉  - 长官
- Captain Connor.   - Sir.
德国人不再铐我们的人了
The Germans have taken the handcuffs off our men.
- 是的,我知道了  - 你知道？
- Yes, I knew about that.   - You knew?
离开伦敦前就知道了
I knew before I left London.
那些人的手铐要立即拿掉
Then those men must be unshackled at once.
不急,长官
Not just yet, sir.
上尉,我受命与你合作,并不是放弃指挥权
Captain, I'm instructed to cooperate with you, not relinquish my command.
不是,长官
Not at all, sir.
但你必须按情报部的要求做
But you see, you must comply with what the lntelligence mission requires.
何况我来这里并非只为解决暴乱问题
And I didn't come here just to put down a riot.
你在正式要求我违犯日内瓦协议？
Are you formally requesting me to contravene the Geneva Convention?
只是几个小时
For a few hours is all.
好吧,康纳上尉
Very well, Captain Connor.
我相信今日之事对你极有好处
I'm sure today's episode can only redound to your credit.
长官
Sir.
我要一个所有受伤人员的名单
I want a complete list of the numbers and injuries to our men.
现场80人,无误,长官
Eighty present and correct, sir.
继续,军士
Carry on, Sergeant.
长官,4队检查完毕,全部在场,点名完毕
Sir, checked parade four. All present and accounted for.
解散！
Parade, dismiss!
我有许可去看望我的人
I have permission to check on the condition of my men.
请进
Yes, sir. Go inside, please.
这此看起来象刀伤
These look like knife cuts.
他失去很多血,把他放床上
He lost a lot of blood. Put him to bed.
诺伊尔呢？
Where's Neuchl?
在那小房间里
In that little room.
- 音乐让你烦吗,长官？  - 没有
- Does the music bother you, sir?   - Not at all.
是为了治疗,长官。德国人喜欢这类
It's a therapy, of course, sir. Germans are fond of this kind of thing.
我一直在收集古典音乐,因为--
I've always collected classical music because--
你有医用白兰地吗？
Have you any of that medical brandy?
有,长官
Y es, sir.
喝一杯吗,上尉？
Will you have a drink, Captain?
为什么不让我看一个我的人？
Do I understand you refuse me the right to see one of my men?
- 一杯白兰地,下士  - 是,长官
- Just the one brandy, Corporal, please.   - Y es, sir.
他并不急于见你的
Well, he doesn't seem to be too anxious to see you.
他逃离了你的那帮畜生,对不？
He got away from those brutes of yours, didn't he?
他们几乎杀了他
They nearly killed him.
他由首席外科医生看护
He's under the care of the chief surgeon.
你这爱尔兰人真是不可思议,上尉
You lrish are just fabulous, Captain.
你真是继承了著名的爱尔兰想象力
You really have got that famous lrish imagination.
但你今早的水造成了如此混乱
But your water sports this morning made such a confusion.
谁知道你看见了什么？
Who knows what you saw?
看见了什么我知道,我看见一个人逃跑
I know what I saw. I saw a man tryin' to escape.
不是我和你唱反调,上尉
I'm not contradicting you really, Captain.
你或许看见企图逃跑
You may have seen an attempted escape.
哪个犯人不想逃跑？
Is it not the duty of all prisoners to try?
- 长官  - 谢谢,下士
- Sir.   - Thank you, Corporal.
托斯卡尼尼？
Toscanini?
富特旺勒更棒
Furtwangler does it better.
顺便说一下,德国营已经取消了英国战俘的手铐
By the way, the German camps have taken the shackles off the British prisoners.
我们会很快做出回应
And we shall reciprocate very soon.
当然,你的人造成了不小的破坏
Of course, your lads did quite a bit of damage.
我们将从他们工资里扣
We'll have to deduct that from their pay.
眼下就没事了,上尉
And that will be all for now, Captain.
你可去看你的人
You'll want to see your men.
上尉,扣我的工资补偿损失
And Captain, deduct the damages from my pay.
- 谢谢  - 你做的已经够多了
- Thank you.   - You've done too much as it is.
看着那个人,让他尽快离开
Keep your eye on that one. See that he leaves soon.
没我同意不许任何人进去
And don't let anyone else in without my authorization.
在这里
There they are.
把这些书带给犯人,我检查过了
Take these books to the prisoners. I've inspected them.
这些都是水手的吗？
This is all the Kriegsmariners?
是的,我分捡出来的
Y es. I separated them.
我看不懂德文
I don't read German all that well.
我甚至不知道我在找什么
I don't even know what the hell I'm lookin' for.
- 那是什么？  - 永恒
- What's that?   - Ewigkeit.
"亲爱的妻子,象是已经隔了很久
"My dear wife, it has seemed like an eternity...
自从我上次亲你的胸部
since last I kissed your bosom...
and slept with my arms entwined...
让你睡在我的怀里
around your body."
抱着你的玉体
你一整天都在读这种情书？
You read these horny letters all day?
- 这是邮局的职责  - 是吗？
- That's the function of the post office.   - lt is?
"萝卜长得很好,亲爱的
"The turnip fields are growing, dear...
我们还要排练几部莎士比亚的戏.
and we are going to do several plays by Shakespeare.
真希望你在我身边,能拥抱你,抚摸你的胸部"
I wish I had you with me now to put my arms around and feel your bosom."
胸部,胸部,胸部
Bosom, bosom, bosom.
为什么他们在日期前放罗马数字？
Why do they put that Roman numeral in the date?
- 什么日期？  - 有罗马数字的日期
- What date?   - The date has a Roman numeral in it.
- 你注意到过吗？  - 以前从没注意过
- You ever notice that?   - I never noticed that before.
有个怪怪的小7
He's got that queer little German seven...
还有1和2,但用罗马数字开头
and the one and the two, but it starts off with a Roman numeral.
就要有个伦敦的破译人员来这里
We're gonna get us a code man down here from London...
让他看看这些情书
and have him take a look at these horny letters.
回床上去！听到没有？
Get back to bed! Do you hear me?
注意！他们有个人质！马上回到床上去！
Look out! They've got a hostage! Get back to your beds immediately!
我让你久等了吗,威利？
Have I kept you waitin', Willi?
这是你的监狱,上尉。我们听你的命令行事
It's your prison, Captain. We follow your orders.
你下达了你的命令,没有吗？
You have imposed your kind of order, haven't you?
- 你和他熟吗？  - 不
- Did you know him well?   - No.
他叫什么名字？你知道的
What's his name? You know that.
鲁珀特・诺伊尔
Rupert Neuchl.
在你们的医院记录中有
You have it on your hospital report.
我是说,他在日间肯定苏醒过的
I mean, he must have regained consciousness during the day.
他上吊死了
He hanged himself.
你要那样通知他家人,还是我来？
Do you want to write that to his family, or should I do it?
那没必要
It won't be necessary.
- 他为何上吊？  - 他懦弱
- Why'd he hang himself?   - He was weak.
他是同性恋。为何问我？
He was a homosexual. Why do you ask me?
我们问了病房中所有的人,当然他们什么也没看见
We asked everyone else in the ward. They didn't see anything, of course.
你是负责人,他为什么要死？
You're the commanding officer. Why'd he die?
上尉,他死在你的监禁中
Captain, he died under your custody.
我想我闻到了白兰地
I smell cognac, I think.
我想你是闻到了爱尔兰威士忌
You smell lrish whiskey, I think.
- 给你  - 谢谢
- There you are.   - Thank you.
很遗憾,尸体总不能与守灵人同乐
It's a pity the corpse never enjoys the wake.
在黄泉路上也有个好人聊天
A hell of a nice fellow to talk to, though.
你喝点,鲁珀特
Here's to you, Rupert.
你的德语-- 你今天发音很好
Your German-- you're pronouncing it very good today.
你的英语发音也很好
You're pronouncin' your English very good too.
你在哪里学的英语,威利？
Where'd you learn English, Willi?
不莱梅启动学院,10年了
Bremen UnterZeeboot Academie, ten years ago.
- 你多大？  - 27岁
- How old are you?   - Twenty-seven.
那你就有幸在希特勒冲锋队干几年了
You must've had a couple of years in the Hitler Youth Camp then, with some luck.
很幸运
A lot of luck.
2年
Two years.
你呢？
And you?
我什么？
Me what?
- 多大？  - 44岁
- I mean, how old?   - I'm 44.
- 还很健康  - 我很好,谢谢
- Still very much alive.   - I'm quite well, thanks.
你这新官给人印象深刻
I mean, your new command is very much impressed.
有个卫兵今天告诉我
One of those nice elderly British guards told me today...
你是个惹麻烦的记者
you were a hell of a journalist.
没错,我是个惹麻烦的记者。我可让你出名,威利
That's true. I'm a hell of a journalist. I could make you famous, Willi.
那为不告诉我这老不死的记者,这人为何而死呢？
Now why don't you tell the lively old crime reporter why the man's dead?
你想让我说我杀了他,为什么？
You expect me to tell you that I killed him, and why?
不,不必你做
No, you don't have to.
我可看出你乐于杀人
I can see your pleasure in the kill.
是吗？
Can you?
或许你可看见一个相信胜利
Perhaps you can see somebody who believes in the war...
相信他的人民和上司的人
who believes in his people, his leaders.
我们为此而在战争中杀戮,是不？
We kill in a war for those things, huh?
或许你不是
But maybe you don't.
我是说,你作为一个爱尔兰人,却在英国军队当上尉
I mean, you're lrish and you're a captain in the British army.
这只英国军队已经杀你爱尔兰同胞几个世纪
That same British army that has killed your own lrish people for centuries.
你到底信仰什么？听谁的命令？
What do you really believe in? What kind of order?
信谁的法律？
What laws do you obey?
嗯,我只服从不得不服从的法律
Well, I obey as few laws as I have to.
我也不是个循规蹈矩的人
And I'm not much of a one for order.
我想是顺其自然吧
It has to be, I suppose...
但规矩就是规矩,是不是？
but there's order and then there's order, isn't there?
死也是一种规矩,对不？
Death is a kind of order, isn't it?
我是说,诺伊尔,他现在很守规矩
I mean, Neuchl there, he's all in order now.
但是威利,你的人很不地道
But, Willi, that's an awful lot of shit about your people.
就我所知,你杀了2个人
You've killed two of them that I know of.
那不对
That's not true.
你杀了他,可能也杀了你的上司
You killed him and you probably killed your commanding officer as well.
我看你要为此受铰刑
And for that I'm goin' to see you hang.
你也乐于杀人吧？
You enjoy killing too, huh?
- 考科斯先生  - 不是吗,康纳上尉？
- Mr. Cox.   - Do you not, Captain Connor?
护送上尉去营地
See that the Captain's escorted back to his quarters, if you please.
开门！
Gate, gentlemen!
康纳想让我以为诺伊尔跟他说了什么
Connor wants me to think that Neuchl told him something.
我想没什么,但说不准
I don't think it was much. I'm not sure.
康纳用德语对我说 '28水手'
'28 Submariners' Connor said to me in German.
上帝！
My God!
他现在也没招
He will do nothing for the moment.
但他会证明我杀了诺伊尔
But he'll try to prove I killed Neuchl.
我们要提前
Meanwhile we go ahead of schedule.
霍奇鲍尔和施密特星期五才回来
Hochbauer and Schmidt won't be back until Friday.
地道5天内挖不到小河
The tunnel won't reach the stream for five days.
告诉昂格尔不挖到小河
Tell Unger not to go to the stream.
转向警卫房下面
Divert and go under the Guard house.
那短多了
It's much shorter.
别让人知道
Don't let the men know it.
要提前
Go ahead of schedule.
是我们的联络人
That's our contact.
坐顺路车吗？
Can I give you boys a lift?
他们写些什么,中尉？
What are they writing home about, Lieutenant?
我还不知道
I can't really tell yet.
象是机器码,如你所见--
It's a question of assembling the basic code pattern. As you see--
- 什么时候能好？  - 很难说
- When will you know anything?   - Hard to say.
一天,若有变异,也许要一周
Could be a day, could be a week if there are variations.
但我们不必靠破译知道有麻烦
But we don't have to wait for a decoded message to know that we have trouble.
显然是施莱特策划的
Obviously Schleutter's at the center of it.
我们要把他移去布莱克浦
We must transfer him to Blackpool.
- 我需要他再呆这里一段时间  - 你需要他？
- I need him here a bit longer.   - You need him?
他策划的,但策划的什么？若他去布莱克浦,我就查不出来了
He's at the center, but of what? I can't find out if he's in Blackpool.
你必须尽快阻塞旧地道
You must block the old tunnel and be as quick as you can with this one.
讨厌的事,但必须做
Lousy work but necessary.
你在营地遇到麻烦吗,考科斯？
Have you met any resistance in the barracks, Mr. Cox?
没有？好
Nothing? Good.
不管发生任何事都,要直接通知我
Well, inform me directly if anything at all happens.
是。谢谢,上校
Y es. Thank you, Sergeant Major.
进来,康纳上尉。我想你应该知道我们在干什么
Come in, Captain Connor. I think you ought to know we're onto something.
谢谢
Thank you.
象是有28个水手想逃跑
It appears that 28 submariners are due to escape.
有艘潜艇来接他们
There's a U-boat coming to pick them up.
"可用U-841。派28人。地点,时间同意"
"U-841 available. Assign 28 men. Location, date agreeable."
- 地点时间呢？  - 我们查了所有的信
- What's the location and date?   - We checked all the letters.
约定的时间肯定在以前收到的东西里
Specific time must've been set before in something they received earlier.
没关系,我们现在就进去阻止他们
It doesn't matter. We'll move in now and break it up.
肯定有地道,宁可拆除所有房子也要找到它
There's got to be a tunnel. We'll pull every barracks apart until we find it.
中尉,请出去一会好吗？
Lieutenant, could you excuse us a minute, please?
去喝杯咖啡之类的
Go and have a cup of coffee or something.
让他们走怎么样？
What if we were to let 'em go?
这样,我们可跟踪找到集合点和潜艇
Then we could follow and find out where the rendezvous is and land the sub.
威利会喜欢吗？
How'd Willi like that?
准许逃跑？
Permit the escape?
地道出口肯定在围墙50码之内
The tunnel's got to come up within 50 yards of that fence.
我们只要派出巡逻,看他们从哪里出来
All we have to do is put patrols out there, see where they come through.
我们保持无线电联系
We keep radio contact.
然后通知军队和地方警察,一直布置到海岸
Then we inform the military and civilian police all the way out to the coast.
最后抢夺潜艇,抓住犯人
Then we nab the sub and the whole lot.
我的职责是管理战俘营,负责里面的战俘
My job is to run this camp and account for the prisoners in it.
奇怪的是,那并不包括允许28人逃走
And curiously enough that doesn't include letting 28 of them escape...
来延长你的军队生涯,上尉
to further your military career, Captain.
现在,我们的人正在按我的命令搜索德国监舍
Under my instructions at this moment, our men are searching German barracks.
- 佩里  - 是佩里上校,上尉！
- Perry.   - It's Major Perry, Captain!
我是你的上级,你应该尊重官衔
I'm your superior officer and you will respect the rank.
我才不管你什么官衔,或任何人的
I don't give a damn about your bloody rank, or anyone else's.
我被派来是执行任务
I got sent up here to do a job.
我要查出暴乱背后的阴谋
I'm supposed to find out what's behind that break.
若你不赞成我的作法,就打电话给克尔将军中止我的工作
If you don't like what I'm doing, call General Kerr and have him relieve me.
把人叫回来,停止搜索
Now bring the men back and stop that search.
作战部给了你特权
The War Office has given you a unique authority here.
我想我必须服从
I suppose I must yield to it.
尽管我相信你是错的,并且你是个自负的傻瓜
Even though I believe you to be mistaken and an arrogant fool.
我来下命令,上尉
I'll give the order, Captain.
然后给伦敦打电话,让他们调走我们之一
Then I'll phone London and have them remove one of us...
避开这难以忍受的状况
from this intolerable situation.
搜索取消了,东西放回
Search has been called off. Everything back.
为什么放弃搜索,上尉？
Why give up the search, Captain?
长官！有件东西你该看看
Sir! There's something in here you ought to see, sir.
说这人一直在生病,长官
And this one's just been sick, sir.
卡什曼,我们要点名
Mr. Cashman, we'll have a roll call.
是,长官。继续,军士
Yes, sir. Carry on, Sergeant.
- 他们走了多久了  - 谁？
- How long have they been away with--   - Who?
给我这两个逃犯的名字
I want the names of these two that escaped.
对不起,我不认识他们
Sorry. I didn't know them personally.
封锁营地,等待命令
Seal off the barracks until further orders.
看来点名要很久的,威利
It's very likely to be a long roll call, Willi.
潜艇在海上干得不错,空军不行
Submarines do well in water, not the Luftwaffe.
放弃吧,施吕特
Give it up, Schluetter.
17 小时
17 hours.
潜艇能近得收到信号
The truck will be close enough to signal.
你是说今晚走？
You mean to go tonight?
士兵！
Soldier!
我要和考科斯上校讲话
I want to speak to Sergeant Major Cox.
施莱特上尉交出了2逃犯的名单
Captain Schleutter gave us the names of the two men who escaped.
他下令他的人配合点名
He's instructed his men to stand by for roll call.
为什么他现在屈服了？
Why the hell does he bother to knuckle under now?
我去拿花名册
I'll get identifications on the wire, sir.
卫兵,打开监舍,让这帮狗娘养的进去避雨
Guards. Open the barracks and let the bastards in out of the rain.
不舒服的一天,先生们
It's been an uncomfortable day gentlemen.
晾干
Dry off.
你总是没完,上尉？
You never stop, eh Captain?
你明天的计划是什么？
What are your plans for tomorrow?
先吃饭,然后做梦会女人
First a meal and dreams of warm women.
这他妈的蠢蛋,根本不管我们是否会得肺炎
The damn fool doesn't care if we all get pneumonia.
住口！
Shut up!
别象诺伊尔那样找死
Don't hang yourself like Neuchl.
通知有关人熄灯后走
Tell the men that we go right after lights out.
我们应该等康纳不太警觉时
We should wait until Connor is less alert.
今晚不走也行的
We don't have to go tonight.
康纳的人手今晚都在监舍里
Connor will have this hands full in this barracks tonight.
熄灯后1小时我们在2号房见
We meet in No. 2 barracks an hour after lights out.
能完成吗？
Are we going to make it?
快完成了
We've almost finished.
这雨的压力很大
The rain has put a bad strain on the support.
我们会好的,我肯定
We'll be alright, I'm sure.
给我们倒杯酒,考科斯
Pour us a drink, Mr. Cox.
给外面的伙计送些去
Take some of that from the stores and give it to the lads outside.
谢谢长官,他们会感谢的
Thank you, sir. The old sweats'll appreciate that.
早晨把诺伊尔的朋友带来,他叫什么来着
In the morning get me that friend of Neuchl's-- what's his name--
伯杰中尉
Lieutenant Berger.
救命！
Help!
卫兵！快出来！快,快！
Guards! Come on out of there! Come on. Move, move!
到我们这里来！去看看另一边！
Let's have you! Go look on the other side!
快！
Come on!
- 哪里？  - 我不知道
- Which one?   - I don't know.
塔楼,几号房？
Hello, towers. Which one?
3号房,象是整个房子陷进去了
Barracks three. Looks like the whole damned thing caved in.
谢谢
Thanks.
见他妈的鬼！
Bloody hell!
快,别他妈的挡路！快！快！
Come on. Out of the bloody way! Move! Out! Out!
对,搬开这些垃圾
Right. Let's get through this rubbish.
你在看什么？继续走
What are you looking at? Get moving.
走  - 安静  - 走！
Go   - quietly   - Go!
埃布尔、贝克、查利,与我和大门保持无线联系
Patrols Able, Baker, Charlie, keep in radio contact with me and the main gate.
拿斧子来
Give us an axe.
拿斧子劈开其它门
Get an axe and smash the other door down.
让这些人回床位,查铺
Get this lot back in their beds and count 'em.
让这些人回床检查
Get the men back to their beds for a check.
霍尔茨  - 弄塌它！
Now Holtz   - collapse it!
笨蛋,你差点把我们都弄死了
Clumsy idiot, you could have killed us all.
已经死了6人,长官
Six dead so far, sir.
找到该死的地道
Find the damned tunnel.
- 发生了什么事？  - 我不太清楚,长官
- What the hell's going on now?   - I don't exactly know, sir.
- 3号房房顶塌了  - 房顶塌了？
- Number three's roof's collapsed.   - The roof's collapsed?
是的,长官
Y es, sir.
康纳上尉现在那里
Captain Connor's up there now, sir.
是吗？他派的外部巡逻检查了没？
Is he? Has he checked round his exterior patrols?
- 还没有,长官  - 现在去做
- Not as far as I know, sir.   - Do that now.
继续开
Drive on.
你们去拿担架
You men get the stretcher.
我看看他们查完没有
I'll see if they've got the count, sir.
军士,到大门来,搞个3吨的运伤员
Sergeant, get back down to the main gate and get a three-tonner here for wounded.
- 查完了没有？  - 还没有,上校.
- Have you got the count yet?   - Not yet, Major.
只死了10人,康纳
Only ten dead, Connor.
37人失踪
Thirty-seven not accounted for.
我想我们找到了地道,长官
I think we've located the tunnel, sir.
别进,塌了
Hold it. It's collapsed.
是长官,死了10人
Yes, sir. Ten dead.
另有27人在地道塌陷时被困
Another 27 trapped when the tunnel collapsed.
估计施莱特上尉和他们在一起
Presumably Captain Schleutter was with them.
不,长官。要挖几个小时
No, sir. It'll take several hours of digging.
本来可避免的,几小时后我送给你详细报告
It needn't have happened. I'm sending you a complete report in a few hours.
不,长官。他没完成什么
No, sir. He hasn't accomplished a thing.
你可以告诉克尔将军,康纳上尉来这里执行任务
You may inform General Kerr that Captain Connor's mission here...
是个致命错误
has been a fatal mistake.
晚安长官
Good night, sir.
没人,长官。他妈的一个人也没有！
Nothing, sir. Not a bloody one of them!
5号基地,我是康纳
Base Station Five. This is Connor.
给我警察的频道
Give us a police frequency.
A85号地路障已设
Roadblock in position on A85.
警察报告B828路段没有可疑的车
Police report no suspicious traffic on the B828...
正继续向北巡逻
and continue mobile patrols north.
所有单位
All units.
麦肯齐骚乱,逃跑的犯人可能有武器
Per the McKenzie break, escaped prisoners should be considered armed.
所有交警单位请注意
All units station traffic, please copy.
珀斯和阿伯费尔迪东北
Northeast of Perth and Aberfeldy...
东至邓弗姆林...
east to Dunfermline...
南至福尔柯克...
south to Falkirk...
西南至格拉斯哥,西至赖弗里
southwest to Glasgow, west to lnverary.
下列路障即刻启用--
The following roadblocks will go into effect in the immediate area--
麦肯齐和斯特灵之间的33号
Number 33 between McKenzie and Stirling.
这里是格伦加里警局
This is Glengarry police.
我们需要更多的车辆,检查沿海路段
We require extra mobiles to maintain watch on coast road.
格伦加里警局,完毕
Glengarry police, over.
北海岸警队
North Shore coast guards.
空军海防总队
Coastal Command.
我们没收到高沼地北部地段的报告
We have no response from northern moorland's road net.
估计在检查南湖
Presumably still in effect from the Southern Lochs...
至格莱尼湖北部
as far north as Loch Glenny.
所有单位请回答
Case section at Clough here. All units please reply.
重复,所有单位
Please, repeat, all units.
- 长官！克尔将军来了  - 上帝
- Sir! General Kerr's arrived.   - Oh, God.
- 发生了什么？  - 混乱,长官。就那么简单
- What happened?   - Balls-up, sir. Simple as that.
一点也不简单
Nothing simple about it.
比去年加拿大鲍曼维尔战俘营的事更严重
Worse than what happened at Bowmanville Camp in Canada last year...
英国政府认为那是个灾难
and Whitehall thought that was a disaster.
佩里给总参谋部写了详细报告
Perry's made a full report to top staff.
我不责怪他,我本可以避免这事的
I don't blame him. I could have prevented it.
这就是了。现在我们开始吧,老伙计？
That's dead right. Now, let's get back, shall we, old chap?
我不管什么优先级别
I don't care what the priority classification is.
我再要3架飞机
I want three more aircraft.
就是这样
You're damned right I do.
空军海防总队说有几千英里的
Coastal Command say there are several thousand miles...
苏格兰海岸,并到处是伪装
of naturally camouflaged coastline around Scotland...
他们不能搜索遍
and how in the hell can they cover it all.
高沼地北部公路网 -- 没有
Northern moorlands road net-- nothing.
又一个电话,长官
There's another call for you, sir.
恐怕必须调用地方警察,长官
I'm afraid it's essential to use civilian police, sir.
- 重要吗？  - 是
- lmportant?   - Aye.
走吧
Go ahead.
A828号公路上有卡车
There's a truck on the A828.
爆炸品,由警察摩托车护送
Explosives with a police motorcycle escorting it.
没有,先生。爆炸品由燃料动力部管
No, sir. Explosives are under the ministry of Fuel and Power.
在战时从不安排
The escort duty our men are assigned to is never for...
工业或矿上护送任务
industrial or mining purposes during wartime.
- 我们从不派人--  - 非常感谢
- We never assign men for--   - Thanks very much.
基地,这是零468
Base Section, this is Zero 468.
我在巴拉胡利什上空,没有情况,转向北部
I'm over Ballachulish. All clear, turning south.
有辆警察摩托车护送的装爆炸品的卡车
There's an explosives truck with a motorcycle escort...
驶向B828号公路
heading north on Highway B828.
呆在那里,不要靠近
Stay up there. Don't move in close.
罗杰
Roger.
离开他  - 转向右
Let's lose him   - turn right in here.
他们或者去洛恩峡湾或者去林尼
They're either goin' for the Firth of Lorne or else Loch Linnhe.
他们将带我们找到潜艇
And they're gonna lead us right to the sub.
直接到,太好了
Straight away. Splendid.
它必须浮出水面和靠近海滩,是吗？
It has to come to the surface and move in to the beach, doesn't it?
是的,但若找不到他们就有我们受的了
Y eah, but if we miss them, we've had it.
抓住他们,就没事了
Bag them now and call that good.
- 我看不到卡车了  - 上帝保佑
- I have lost contact with the truck.   - Ben, for God's sake.
是侦察机,他失去目标
It's the reconnaissance pilot. He's lost contact.
快  - 扔了这个
Quick   - get rid of that.
失去目标
Lost contact.
建议警察监视B828公路北部
Suggest immediate police surveillance north on Highway B828.
- 我去找飞机  - 我安排运输,长官
- I'll get a plane myself.   - I'll arrange transport, sir.
你们这些人去哪里？
Where are you men going?
去让我们的美国佬舒服些,老爹.
Just going to make our Yank visitors comfy, Dad.
全是家俱...
Load of furniture...
运给马哈迪的美国新基地
for the C.O. at the new American base at Mahaddie.
看
Look.
甚至有给那帮家伙的淋浴
Even a shower attachment for the silly bastard.
要5先令
It's five shillings.
开船！好人
Heave up the tail! Good man.
天黑后什么也看不见
Won't be able to see a bloody thing after dark.
去那边察看
Look-outs up there.
没事
All clear.
伪装卡车
Camouflage the truck.
这是白女士7号
This is White Lady 7.
你在用海军频道,43号机,我没有授权 --
You are on a navy frequency, Flight 43. I have no authorization--
我知道。我正要告诉你,潜艇将浮出且停在那里
I know that. I'm just tellin' you the sub will surface and sit there.
知不知道会在哪里？
Have any idea where that might be?
不知道。我若知道就不用猜了
Hell, no. If I knew, I wouldn't be guessin'.
这是浪费时间
That's a waste of time.
把它推进洞里快走
Let's drive it down this hole and get going.
船先到
The boats first.
你疯了吗？
Have you gone crazy?
停车！
Stop the truck!
这他妈的怎么回事？
What the hell is going on?
是他妈的什么？
Now what the hell?
看到了吗？下去
Do you see that? Go on down there.
我想,是燃烧的垃圾,长官。没其他东西
Burning rubbish I should say, sir. No sign of anything else.
继续走
Go on ahead.
这是白女士7号
This is White Lady 7.
我刚完成X光扫描
I've just completed a sweep of grid 16 X-ray.
18分钟日落
Sunset in 18 minutes.
到时返航
Will turn for home at that time.
E.T.A.,1930.
E.T.A., 1930.
完毕
Out.
我们没有你的飞行计划,43号机。返回基地
We have no flight plan for you, Flight 43. Return to base.
- 我说,你没经授权  - 你怎么会那样想？
- I say, you're not authorized.   - Where'd you get an idea like that?
- 飞行控制  - 他们扯你后腿
- Flight Control.   - They're pullin' your leg.
再飞一圈,我给你搞勋章
Make another run offshore like a good fellow and I'll get you a medal.
快,我在你后面
Hurry, I'm right behind you.
潜艇在那儿。上帝,就是它
There's the sub. Jesus, that's it!
白女士,这里是43号机
White Lady, this is Flight 43.
潜艇在一英里处
Sub's off the point about a mile.
一英里！浮在海面
About a mile! U-boat on the surface.
发动,全速向前
Engine, full ahead.
下到那里,震开他们
Go on down there. Buzz the hell out of 'em.
你能到吗,它要下潜了！
Will you get in there. It'll submerge on you!
我们好象被击中了,长官。最好找个地方降落
Looks like we've been hit, sir. Better find a place to put her down.
探测不到潜艇,请示再次扫描
Asdic reports lost contact with U-boat. Request another sweep.
这是白女士7号呼叫夫人
This is White Lady 7 calling Madam.
潜艇1924年浮出
U-boat submerged 1924.
方位045,偏离顶点航线
Bearing 045 off course head point...
有4个被抛弃的犯人
and boarding four prisoners who were abandoned.
将继续搜寻
Will continue asdic sweep on 19 degrees aft from grid 13 easy.
请求援助
Request assistance.
克尔将军呼叫康纳上尉
General Kerr calling Captain Connor.
快接,康纳
Come in, Connor.
这是克尔将军呼叫海军453频道.
This is General Kerr calling Naval Frequency 453.
威利,我们俩都有麻烦了
Willi, looks like we're both in the shit house.
克尔将军呼叫康纳上尉
General Kerr calling Captain Connor.
快接,康纳
Come in, Connor.